depressionanxietyseries.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Depression, Anxiety & Brain Secrets

_Effective as of May 24, 2018_

Welcome to AutoimmuneSecrets.com (the “Website”), a website is operated by Autoimmune Secrets, LLC (“we” or “us”). Your privacy is very important to us. We made this Privacy Policy to help you know how we collect, use, and share information about you. The practices set forth in this Privacy Policy apply only to this Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website or service provided by us, our affiliates or clients, unless it appears on such website or service.

By using our Website or any features provided through it, or by providing us your personal information, you accept and agree to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. You may not use or otherwise visit our Website unless you agree to this Privacy Policy.

##  **The Information We Collect**

We collect information regarding visitors to our Website to help us operate the site, including to process transactions, communicate with visitors, improve the Website and user experiences, and provide better products and services.

 **The information we collect from visitors to our Website can be categorized as follows:**

Personal Information You Give Us. We only collect personally identifying information (or “personal information”) that you voluntarily provide to us. For example, we typically collect personal information from you when you sign up for our newsletter, place an order, respond to a survey, fill out a form, or otherwise contact us. This personal information can help us identify you as an individual, and may include your name, email address, phone number, mailing address, and credit card information. When ordering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter personal information. You may visit our Website anonymously if you chose not to provide us with any of your personal information.

Automatically collected non-personal information. We may also automatically collect information about you when you visit the Website that does not personally identify you. This non-personal information includes your public Internet Protocol (or “IP”) address, the type of browser or device operating system you use, the website that referred you to our Website, and the amount of time you spend and the specific pages you visit on the Website.

Aggregate information. We may also aggregate information we collect from you with information from other visitors to the Website. For example, such aggregated information may include the number of users who are located in a certain region or have certain characteristics.

##  **How We Use Cookies**

We use cookies – small files put on your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) – to enable the Website to recognize your specific browser and to gather and remember certain information about you and your interactions with the Website. We may compile and aggregate data from cookies to monitor our traffic to the Website and visitor interactions. We may, from time to time, use this aggregated information to assess the performance of our Website and products, and to improve website experiences and products in the future.

 **We do not use cookies and similar items to automatically retrieve personal information from your device without your knowledge.**

If you want to stop, limit, or undo the placement of cookies that may already be on your computer or device, please refer to and adjust your web browser preferences. The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to modify your browser’s settings, such as to stop accepting new cookies, notify you when your browser receives a new cookie, or disable cookies altogether. You can find further information regarding cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org. By deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Website or some of its functionality may be affected.

##  **Protecting Your Personal Information**

Because any system connected to the internet is vulnerable and could be compromised by a hacker or rogue insider, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide us. However, take commercially reasonable measures and employ a variety of security measures to ensure that the personal information you disclose to us is kept secure. For example, we may use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and encryption in connection with certain transactions or the storage of certain information.

##  **Sharing Information with Third Parties**

In the ordinary course of business, we may share your information or make it accessible to certain third parties. These third parties are people or businesses that we do not own, operate, control, or otherwise are not closely affiliated with us by ownership, management, employment, or similar close relationships.

We do not sell your information to third parties, exchange it with them, or otherwise seek to profit by specifically disclosing your information with third parties. We will only provide your personal information to affiliates and third parties to help us process your personal information for the purposes set out in this policy. We may provide your personal information to affiliates and trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or providing services to you. We may permit our vendors and subcontractors to access your personal information, but only in connection with performing services for us. We do not authorize them to use the information for their own benefit or to contact you directly (except on our behalf).

We may also release your information when we believe doing is required by law or legal process, to enforce our Website policies, or protect ours or another’s rights, property, or safety, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual unlawful or otherwise prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud, harassment or other violations of law or the policies of the Website. For example, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information in connection with a bankruptcy proceeding or if we or any of our assets are the subject of a sale or similar corporate transaction, including, but not limited to, a merger, acquisition or change of control.

Unlike your personal information, we may share non-personal information, which does not personally identify you, to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our website’s visitors. Generally, the information provided to or gathered by these service providers will be aggregated non-personal information, such as information gathered from cookies. We do not authorize these service providers to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

##  **GDPR**

The GDPR takes effect on May 25, 2018, and is intended to protect the data of European Union (EU) citizens.

As a company that markets its site, content, products and/or services online we do not specifically target our marketing to the EU or conduct business in or to the EU in any meaningful way. If the data that you provide to us in the course of your use of our site, content, products and/or services is governed by GDPR, we will abide by the relevant portions of the Regulation.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), or are accessing this site from within the EEA, you may have the right to request: access to, correction of, deletion of; portability of; and restriction or objection to processing, of your personal data, from us. This includes the “right to be forgotten.”

To make any of these requests, please contact our GDPR contact at support@autoimmunesecrets.com

##  **The rights of Users**

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

  * Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
  * Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
  * Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
  * Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
  * Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
  * Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
  * Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
  * Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

 **Details about the right to object to processing**

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

 **How to exercise these rights**

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

##  **Links to Third-party Websites**

From time to time as we so chose, we may include or offer products or services of third parties or links to websites that are not operated by us. These third-party websites maintain their own separate, independent privacy policies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites.

We not endorse, verify, or make any representations concerning the accuracy of the information on these third-party websites, or the extent to which they will protect your personal information. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. When you leave our Website to visit a third-party website, you do so at your own risk. We encourage you to read the policies and terms of every website you visit.

We may also integrate social networking services into the Website or offer links to other third-party websites that handle specific functions on our behalf. We do not control such services and are not liable for how they operate. To the extent we may provide you with the ability to use such services in connection with our Website, we do so merely as an accommodation and, like you, are relying upon those third-party services to operate properly and fairly. Information you voluntarily disclose or transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, social network or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others. We are unable to control such uses of your personal information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the personal information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

##  **How Long We Keep Your Information**

We retain personal information you provide us through the Website for as long as necessary for our business purposes. For example, we may retain such information as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. Even if we delete some or all of your personal information, we may continue to retain and use aggregate or non-personal data previously collected.

##  **Children**

We direct our Website, products and services to individuals who are at least 13 years old or older. We do not knowingly collect information from persons under the age of 13 years. If we are made aware that we have received personal information regarding a person under the age of 13, as with any information obtained in violation of this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to locate and remove that information from our records.

If you are under 13 years old, you may only use this Website with the involvement of your parent or guardian.

##  **Reviewing or Changing Your Personal Information and Opting Out**

We do not maintain a process for you to review your personal information we have collected through our Website. You may request changes to your personal information by sending your request to us at **support@autoimmunesecrets.com**

You can also opt-out of any future promotional messages from us by sending an unsubscribe request to us at **support@autoimmunesecrets.com**

We will process your request within a reasonable time after receiving it. However, we are not responsible for removing your personal information from any lists of third parties who have previously been provided with your information according to this Privacy Policy or your consent.

As noted above, you may limit the placement of cookies on your device or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. You may not be able to opt-out of placement of cookies on many mobile devices. However, depending on your mobile device, you may be able to opt out of certain advertisements through their device settings.

##  **Scope of Policy**

This Privacy Policy only applies to visitor information collected through our Website. The Policy does not apply to information collected offline, or by means other than our Website.

##  **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time as we so chose. We will post any changes to the Privacy Policy on this page of the Website. Any changes will be effective when the revised Privacy Policy is posted. You can find the effective date of the current Privacy Policy at the top of this page.

If we otherwise determine that we have made a significant change to this Privacy Policy, we may attempt to notify you of the change by email.

We will not make any changes to this Privacy Policy without your consent that reduce your rights with regard to personal information you provided us.

##  **Inquiries**

Please contact us if you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy. You may email us at support@autoimmunesecrets.com, calling our customer support at 619-630-7183, or writing to us at the address below:

30 N Gould St. STE R,  
Sheridan, WY 82801
